adultvideolink.com 2013-05-21

# - Help section

Help zone

**Adultvideolink.com Privacy Policy**

Welcome to Adultvideolink.com! Please read this privacy policy carefully before using Adultvideolink.com (the "Site"). 

THIS PRIVACY POLICY GOVERNS YOUR USE OF THE SITE, WHICH IS PROVIDED BY EAST MEDIA GROUP, INC. (EMG), THE OWNER OF THE SITE, (THE "OWNER"). BY ACCESSING THE SITE, YOU ARE INDICATING YOUR ACKNOWLEDGMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE BY THE OWNER AT ANY TIME IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION. YOUR USE OF THE SITE AFTER SUCH CHANGES ARE IMPLEMENTED CONSTITUTES YOUR ACKNOWLEDGMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF THE CHANGES. PLEASE CONSULT THIS PRIVACY POLICY REGULARLY. 

Coverage of this Privacy Policy 

This policy covers how the Owner treats personal information that the Owner collects and receives, including information related to your past use of the Site"s products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, credit card information and shipping information, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the Owner does not own or control or to people that the Owner does not employ or does not manage. 

Information Collection and Use 

The Owner receives and stores certain types of information whenever you provide information to the Owner. Information that the Owner collects can be: name and address, e-mail address, credit card information, shipping information, and financial information, including Social Security numbers and Driver"s License numbers. This list is not exclusive, and may be altered without notice based on information that you supply voluntarily. You have the right to refrain from providing to the Owner certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of all of the Site"s features. 

The Owner receives and stores certain types of information whenever you interact with the Site. The most significant information is stored in the form of cookies, or small storage files that transmits your electronic identity to the Web site that you visit. Like most Web sites, the Owner uses cookies to be able to identify you as a return visitor to the Site. 

The Owner uses your information solely in order to process your credit card payment, to facilitate your viewing of the Site and to communicate with you. We also use your information to compile broad demographic and web site usage information about you in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally. The Owner uses your e-mail address to send periodic e-mail newsletters and promotional e-mail to you about services and products offered by the Owner, if such communication has been requested by you. You will not receive any e-mail from the Owner unless you have requested it and you can indicate at any time that you do not wish to receive e-mail information from the Owner. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

The Owner does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * 1\. The Owner provides the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with the Owner under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help the Owner communicate with you about offers from the Owner and the Owner"s marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
  * 2\. The Owner responds to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise the Owner"s legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
  * 3\. The Owner believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Site"s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law; and, 
  * 4\. The Owner transfers information about you if the Owner is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, the Owner will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Cookies 

The Owner may set and access the Site"s cookies on your computer. 

The Owner lets other companies that show advertisements on some of the Site"s pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies" use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to the Site"s cookies. 

The Owner uses Web beacons to access the Site"s cookies inside and outside our network of Web sites and in connection with the Owner products and services. 

Information Security 

To protect the security of your information during transmission, the Owner uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you inputs. 

The Owner reveals only the last five digits of your credit card number when confirming an order. To process an order, it is necessary to transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company. 

To prevent unauthorized access to sensitive information, it is important for you to monitor those who have access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

User Access to Information 

When you access your account, there is a variety of information that you will see. This is designed to allow you to update any changed information and view the information that you entered previously. This information is sensitive, and it is necessary to both protect this information and keep it current in order to have the best experience at the Site. 

User Choices with Regard to Access of Information 

You always have the right to refrain from providing information to the Owner. This may have an impact on use of the Site and on the ease of making purchases or taking advantage of certain unique features of the Site. 

You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "User Access to Information" section above. When you update information, the Owner usually keeps a copy of the prior version for the Owner"s records. 

Miscellaneous 

The Owner may revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting. 

Last updated: January 1, 2013 

© 2003 - 2013 East Media Group, Inc.
